peterglenn.com 2008-04-30

# ski shop, snowboard shop, water ski shop, wakeboard shop, in-line skate shop

**** At Peter Glenn of Vermont, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use information about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. We intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit Peter Glenn of Vermont over the Internet without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name and address. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you.

If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet, we or our business partners may use it to correspond with you, process an order or provide you with a subscription to our mailing list. It is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. 

We have implemented these practices for the Peter Glenn of Vermont website and also continually instruct all of our employees and business partners to honor your privacy with the utmost confidentiality. 

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**

When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. 

When you sign up on our mailing list page, we need only an e-mail address. We use this to send you news about the store and special promotions. 

In the future we may personalize your shopping experience by using your purchases to shape our recommendations about the apparel you wear and other merchandise that might be of interest to you. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage such as clicks, hits and at time which other domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data for trends and statistics to help us develop future design layouts and features of the store. Once this information has been analyzed, we discard it. 

We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality change to the Web site, new Peter Glenn of Vermont services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. 

**How does Peter Glenn of Vermont protect customer information?**

When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access using a combination of firewalls, system authorization and the security of industry-leading relational databases such as SQL Server and Oracle. 

**What are "cookies"?**

There is a technology called "cookies" which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personal identification information, but they do enable us to provide features to improve your shopping experience such as storing items in your shopping cart between visits. 

You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You must have cookies enabled in your browser settings to complete a purchase at Peter Glenn of Vermont. 

**Will Peter Glenn of Vermont disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**

Peter Glenn of Vermont does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. Peter Glenn of Vermont may provide aggregate statistics about our customers as well as sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. 

**Our Commitment**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at Peter Glenn of Vermont possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

**Let us know what you think**

Peter Glenn of Vermont welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please send to [questions@peterglenn.com](mailto:questions@peterglenn.com)
